directoryanalyst.com 2013-03-26

# Privacy Policy - Directory Analyst

## Privacy Policy 

1\. **Directory Analyst**

Directory Analyst your right to the privacy of your personal information you provide us on our web site. To that end, any personal information you provide to Directory Analyst will be known only to two parties: you and Directory Analyst. The following policy is intended to explain how your personal information will be treated as you make use of our site and its features. Personal information includes your name and e-mail addresses, and any other personal information you may provide here. This policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically. 

2\. **Traffic Data**

(1) Each time a visitor comes to Directory Analyst, our server - like most on the Web - collects some basic technical information.

(2) We also count, track and aggregate the visitor's activity into our analysis of general traffic flows at our site. To these ends, we may merge information about visitors and visits into group data; but we will not disclose your individual identity or personally identifiable data.

3\. **E-mail Alert Feature**

After signing up with us, directory owners will receive occasional e-mails. You can request us to unsubscribe your email ID. 

4\. **Other Disclosure of Personal Information**

Directory Analyst will not otherwise use or disclose your personal information without your consent except as requested by government or law enforcement authorities. 

5\. **Unsubscribe and Data Removal Policies**

If you would like to unsubscribe from an Directory Analyst, please send us a email. 

6\. **Other Sites**

Directory Analyst contains many links to other sites on the web. We cannot control and are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other Web sites. If you have any further questions or concerns about our privacy policies and use of personal information, please contact us.
